CAREER PROFILE

A System Administrator with 10+ years of professional experience, specializing in Azure, Agile methodology, technical project management, and IT services. A strong background in building and leading high-performance technical teams to execute IT initiatives and technology transformations for enterprise clients.

EXPERIENCES

System Administrator

2015 - Present

Hexagon AB, Sweden

Developed software to complete daily tasks, reducing the time for completion.

Created an effective and productive online documentation platform to help employees resolve daily issues.

System Administrator

2014 - 2015

Wolters Kluwer N.V., Netherlands

Executed strategic IT system procurement and supplier evaluation to maintain the continuity of operations.

Configured, installed, and maintained hardware and software equipment, including routers and switches.

System Administrator

2012 - 2014

Micro Focus International Plc, United Kingdom

Supported and built the front-end and back-end server systems using Windows Server & VMWare Client.

Reduced the company's operating budget by 10% through strategic and innovative contract renegotiations.



Red Hat Certified Engineer

2020 - 2021

Red Hat (EX294)

The Red Hat Certified Engineer (RHCE) certification is for senior Linux or UNIX system administrators. It helps prove an individual's advanced knowledge and skills related to Red Hat system administration and managing systems in DevOps environments. Automation represents a significant component of these environments, and the RHCE certification expects candidates to know how to automate the deployment, management and support of multisystem environments.

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

2019 - 2020

Cisco (200-301)

CCNA certification proves you have what it takes to navigate the ever-changing landscape of IT. CCNA exam covers networking fundamentals, IP services, security fundamentals, automation and programmability. Designed for agility and versatility, CCNA validates that you have the skills required to manage and optimize today's most advanced networks.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCY





System Administrator

- → hello@ndou.com
- **J** +321 345 67891
- U Europe/Athens Timezone
- S blogs.igalia.com/nzimmermann/
- ndou
- nikos788
- y @ndou
- Resume PDF

EDUCATION

MSc in Pervasive and Mobile Computing Systems

Hellenic Open University

BSc in Computer Science
Hellenic Open University

LANGUAGES

Greek (Native)

English (Professional)

INTERESTS

Running

Swimming

ABOUT THEME

How to use?

☆ Star 2,767